sending me with fireworks confetti in her hair said you're such a lovely soul with that calculator
stare but i was just a chess piece in a feud i didn't choose a temporary favorite in her very
Why pretending to be clean?
I thought it was connection
Turns out it was theater
A one-woman production call
How can I be meaner?
I was good enough for midnight talks
For spiral rants and victim unlawfuls
But when the script got rewritten fast
She cut my name from every care
Till Tuesday
Holy till the fall
Then suddenly I'm toxic
The villain after all
Don't contact me, she tells me
With the curtains dramatic drawn
Then she floats into my panel
Like a ghost in Mr. Don
Calls me some grand monster
Says I'm darkness doom and doom me up
Funny how I was a snake
Right up until I got less useful
To a junior empire
Now I'm the big disaster
That's rich coming from the patrons
Ain't a change in every pastor
She found herself a champion
A knight in shining chrome
Posted him like Rescumer
Said finally I'm home
Just hit the wall
She whippers then appears where I live on air like boundaries off of peasants and hypocrisy's couture the way
Now I'm some spiritual trafficker. What a deluxe invention. There's not a charge
It's fanfiction with a persecution pension
No for the thumbnail, pitchfork for the rage
One day you're her confidant, the next day you're her curse
Every friendship gets a trailer, every fallout gets rehearsed
And I'm not even mad now, I mostly want popcorn
Such a beast, baby, why haunt my little show?
Why bang on the cathedral door you swore you'd never know?
Don't contact me, OK, cool her.
Then why are you enrolling, memorizing every word?
Contact me, fine by me.
Then why do you keep orbiting my so-called monstrosity?
I would.
Who borrowed truth for leverage and performed pain with style
I'll be over here still breathing still speaking still
Humors, humor is my objective.
I thought it was funny, so you think it doesn't.
I don't think she thought it was funny either.
Alexander McQueen was laughing his butt off.
I don't know.
I mean, it's already done.
I mean, I'd say what?
You know what she did to me last night, Joni?
You don't know what she did to me last night.
Or today, I mean, today she struck me today,
but last night, she was even worse.
Her might feel even more.
There's a reason.
You know, I went to her chat and I said,
I don't know if you're mad at me or I'm blocked or whatever.
I just want to say, sorry, I wish you well.
I love you and have a blessed evening.
That's what I said to her in her chat.
She said, oh, this person, this guy,
doesn't respect my boundaries,
even though she came to my chat on my panel
after she said, oh, don't contact me.
She came herself, okay?
It's like giving love, repaid with stripping acid in my face or whatever.
I don't know.
Hurt my feelings.
So maybe it is stupid or reactive or whatever.
I don't know.
Everyone says, oh, the only good videos I do maybe are the funny ones.
I'm trying to be funny.
She's in a mask.
Like Jesus, love, yeah, love, right?
How does Jesus, how does Jesus get repaid for loving?
Oh, let's nail him on a cross.
Alex gets it.
It's wearing a mask.
It's just, all I said, I didn't say,
oh, here's Alexander's picture and based this on her.
I just said, a black lady in a mask.
Tall black lady in a mask with nice tits.
I didn't say that part.
I'm just kidding.
No, Katrina, it wasn't about that video.
It was about a photo with me and her.
It was our photo at dinner when we went to dinner.
It wasn't that, she didn't strike over that video.
She struck over a picture of us at dinner
or we're smiling and I just wanted to show,
hey, we met and we were happy at one point.
I don't know.
It's okay, it's okay.
Guys, guys, it's my fault, right?
It's just, it's my fault, right?
Yeah, it's okay.
Yeah, that didn't, even though I called it
and I was like, what should I call it?
Should I say Alexander Mayer?
I was like, no, I'll just call it, oh, Alexandra.
Which, and she showed it a million times too, right?
I mean, I'll say it did look like Tommy James. It was a little bit, it did look like Tommy James, a big fat ginger.
Do you know what he said about her?
Well, you, you don't, but on Sam-Anne's panel, she came on his panel, who she calls PDF and
spiritual trafficker and all this stuff, or not spiritual trafficker, actual human trafficker,
right? But she'll go on his show, give him the exclusive about Tommy James humiliating her.
It's okay. You deserve a drink. I deserve a drink too. I deserve a drink too.
Oh yeah, but you know what? It's like
I'll make them regret it.
They want me to stop?
How about I'm just getting started?
How about I'm just getting started, ladies?
Let me go through, let me go through everything.
Because Bita struck me and Alexandra struck me,
so I don't have a choice, it's, you know, I don't have a choice.
You know what a strike is, you know what strike means?
Strike means hitting the, it's like a hit.
It's like a, and you only get three of them, right?
I don't want to leave.
I want to be here.
This is my life.
This is my baby.
It's like, Jesus was sacrificed at 33.
Yeah, I'm a Jesus 2.0 44
That I think there are they there was 55 I think right I think you know I'd be in her 70s. I'm sure I
Don't want to leave
It lasts three months, but you only get three, you know, but they can take it down they can take them down in a second
they're not going to. You know why? Because they're Bita and Alexandra.
They last three months. Yeah, it's not only three months though. It's like, what, so the next three months?
Oh my gosh, she does look fat in that picture.
She does.
I didn't know.
But she posted that.
She goes, you blamed it on TripKick's video.
I told you not to use my X photo.
You continued, stop it.
And then she struck me.
And so I said, you could have asked before,
B-Tard, you're done.
I asked you before, you snuck it in the TripKick video.
No, TripKick snuck it in.
Tripkix knuck it in. I know but now I have to see I have I have this website
I was doing called the cold cold codex is gonna have every one of my episodes everybody
It's on the show guys. I've spent hundreds of dollars doing this website. Oh my god. Here he comes. He's doing it again
He's nice this
Yeah, I'll do it. I'll try I'll try I'll try but now I have to have everything private
And so I can't have my cold codex done which I've been working on
And stuff, okay, I mean, I'll try.
I'm gonna try, I have to private everything.
Yeah, it's called the Codex, yep.
It will have every single person that's been on the panel.
It'll have every show, it'll have quotes,
it'll have, it's like a Wikipedia page.
It's not like Alexander said,
where it's like a Wikipedia, like harassing people
or trying to, what she says is that it's a...
A black man like I'm turning black male on the Wikipedia even though if you want your your entry taken down
They'll be a thousand dollars. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. It's called
Colts codex colt codex dot me. I think it's called
I'll show I think I might have some of it up right now, but I'll show you what it looks like so far. Oh
It's really cool actually the guys look just just to show that I'm not just a little bullshit
I'm actually somebody that like cares and like tries look
Into the circle
Okay, and so it has there's the because it's not working perfectly right psyche verse it mean it's like I'm trying my best
See that my first day like when I started doing this the live streams January 28th and Gateway open
First meditation and beginning of journey with those week in rituals and ceremonies the schedule guys
It was it was gonna be cool. It was gonna be cool. I was trying to do something fun can finally cool, you know for
I don't know if anybody else is doing this shit, but I'm trying to do something cool, right?
like I'm
So yeah, this was gonna have everything on it
Right, you can join the cult blah blah blah blah. There's gonna be
All all this cool stuff join the mailing list. I don't know. Does it look okay? I mean, I thought it looked cool
I thought I was doing something
different
I thought I was a kind of different person in this community and stuff like that.
I thought I was kind of like a cool person, like has created ideas.
I was going to try to like revolutionize the YouTube thing.
I was going to try to help everybody in this community.
Did anybody say to Bita, hey, how about taking a strike down?
No, but it was sweepy.
Oh my God.
You know, everyone.
Oh my up in arms.
Oh my, and it's all me.
And I was like, okay, I'll take it down, even though it's,
oh, here's an eating McDonald's,
his big, big mac and he has a dirty,
his tan one's dirty,
because I put it in the heater and stuff, you know?
And so, yeah, they got dirty, but whatever.
I mean, it's like, I don't know.
I thought it was looking cool.
I remember putting a lot of money into it,
trying to make it cool and stuff, but no, no, no, no.
It's all it's all done. It's all done my hundreds of dollars my every every dime I made on the show I put towards
improving stuff
Making it cool having trying to have a website and stuff like that
Gonna have every every it's gonna try to like promote every show
Even people that hate me I'd promote. I mean, I'm stupid, right?
Look at it. Look at how cool it is when I started up. Let me start it up. Look how cool it is
Okay, no, no. Yeah, I'm just a piece of shit and garbage. I have no creative ideas
I'm not trying to do anything special for anybody. I wasn't trying to help people, right?
This is garbage, I'm just a garbage person. All my stuff sucks. I just suck. I just suck.
Mean I'm trying so hard. I mean it's like and it was supposed to be special and guys and also like I would have put
Beta and I would put Alexander on this web on my
You can see my own my own channel. Look look at my own channel. This is my page like look
And guys and my friend just died too. Did they make hair now? I mean, yeah, some people do
I mean do they care? No, but I'll show you look look look at this. I
Will try to I'll try to if I have to do a rumble if I have to go to kick
What do you guys follow me over there?
I know it's hard.
I know it's like, you know,
to get to type another like website in and go,
and it's like, you know,
I was trying to do cool stuff for the community.
Maybe what other people say, I try.
I was trying to do something different.
I think there's like a lot of bullshit
just goes on and stuff right.
And I was like, I wanted to do something
kind of cool and different.
So here's my channel, you're a whole once again.
Here's my page like look and I know and beat is not on there or anything but look so psyche recommends dj. Electra summer
banny
money for 20 trishelicious
clumsy being gang chona the k8 show capricorn soul tribe elisa jordana
The oceans who Danny stranger who unfortunately just passed away. I'm so sorry Danny
There's more people too. I can only count that many on them. There's this this guy and well
There's Lucifer Beelzebub. There's Empress Janet who doesn't fuck with me anymore
But you know, there's many Manson who I just saw many Manson with vagina and stuff
With a big you look pregnant I don't know what's going on there. There's Lone May. He's really cute guy
Prairie winds and wildflowers Trident
Scribbles, hey, they're spunky
I tried, I tried.
It was Danny, it was thinking he looked cute in that picture.
Just two weeks ago, I was like hanging out with him.
I sent my chat over there.
Everyone liked him, I don't know how he died.
Know how he died he got shot several times in the chest, but
And if you if you want if you have a channel put your channel up there, too
I think I got it almost everyone. I'm also trying to do psyche versions of like that. They're everyone there
Actually, I'm trying to help
people like I don't understand
And how I'm the biggest piece of garbage in the world
None of these people really being talked to me really I mean cake cake comes here
Benny came last night. That was so cool. Benny came. Did you see the police come last night? That was crazy
the police came
The police came last night to my house and
And and guys and I did tell the police. Yeah, I'm a huge YouTube celebrity the guy
I was it was me. I was being sarcastic a little bit. It was I was I don't think I'm anything special, okay?
You know you got a kick over there, too
promote you Nick
Promote me yesterday. There's a lady. I get a reading. She'd love to read love your reading and everyone likes a reading
I don't really anybody I do a reading for no one's ever said. Oh, that was bad
Yeah, it was a party last night the police came and
And I say I'm a big YouTube celebrity like you come outside sir
I open the door came outside. There's seven cops outside of my house. It's like that was I was like what was it?
Well, it was like basically like I was like, I don't know if I want to open the door for seven cops
But I did.
Paige was here earlier.
She came by a little bit earlier and said hi and stuff.
And she's like, well, she's like, oh,
wouldn't it be nice if Paige was to say to Bita,
hey Beats, hey Bita juice.
Wouldn't it be nice if I should, yeah,
but I am, I was on stream, man.
If, I mean, I'm not saying Paige,
you don't have to do anything for me.
No, nobody has to do anything for me.
to be to to be to juice. Hey, be to remember like
We were all friends at one point and this like laughing having a good time and
What happened
Can you can you like maybe take down the strike as a good as a good faith a good faith?
No
She doesn't know she doesn't owe me anything. Yeah
Yeah, she would go hey beats
Beedah doesn't have a heart, that's a problem.
She doesn't have a heart.
I don't know what happened to her in her life.
Maybe something bad happened to her or something like that.
She doesn't have a heart.
I looked, I looked once.
In the astral world, I went to Beedah
and I opened a little, little heart door
and there was like this little like monster in there.
So it was like a scary.
And that, and he was like, I'm really Peter.
I'm really Peter.
It was like, it's like a little black monster.
I'm not kidding.
People think I joke about, it was a monster.
That's her real self.
You know what's inside Paige?
Paige's heart.
I open it, there's like a little, like, happy, like, there's a whole, like, little happy,
all this, all this, like, nice little, like, dud, dud, dud, dud, dud, dud, dud, dud, dud.
There's like a little, like, it's like, Cirque de Soleil, French Canadian Mines or something
in there, just juggling in, it's all, it was, it was cute, pay, like, pay, that's a good
hearted person, good hearted person, you know what's inside my heart, the same kind of thing.
not Cirque du Soleil because I'm more American, but there's like Marcel Marceau kind of looking
mime in there. Yeah, there's a big Canadian talking dildo in Paige's heart. I don't know. I'm just kidding.
Right. Katrina knows Paige is like there's like rainbows and like unicorns farting and ice cream.
They're like they're shitting ice cream and shit like that in Paige's heart.
Right beat as hard. There's just like some some scary monster. I
Don't know with it. I just closed it and like this backed away slowly. I don't know. I was like, what is that a gin?
Because I think it really meant a gin. I think it was like the king of the gin
What's his name
Something about pleasure. It's like some kind of pleasure. What's the guy? What's it? What's the?
Look for the can of beer called fluffy baby ducks. Do you want to see look at this cat?
Guys my cats. I'm sorry. I'm
I'm an abusive person. I'm gonna I'm just a cat abuser, right?
She's a butt plug in her. I'm a cat abuser read this cat
Do I bother you? Am I bothering you?
You my friend
You're my friend, huh?
It's Purin at me
I'm my bad to you guys my bad. I'm a bad person
Look at this cat look guys look
They're all around me. They just look I mean it's like my little circle. These are my little my little family
Oh, I'm a terrible abusive, I'm abusive to cats and whatever.
This is my best friend, right?
Look at this guy.
I'm a monster guys, right?
I wanna sit around.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, you're comfy.
Lola, Lola, you're comfy.
Hi, I see you.
Lola has a little black mouth, really.
Yeah, I'm a monster guys.
I am, I'm bad, I'm bad.
You're afraid of me because I'm at my and I choke. Do I choke you?
I'm just a bad person, huh? I choke you
Alex I found piggy
My friend too Alex McQueen
What I do cameo casino, what did I do? Tell me I want to hear tell me I
Don't know what I did. I mean I did I've done a lot. What I've done a lot of things in life
What I do what I do that was so bad
But it was so bad. I give you a hug. Are you my friend? I
Mean guys if I was if I was bad the cat do you think you would run you think you would like say oh
Oh, I mean, I'm bothered by this person.
Oh, this is an abusive person.
Do you think he would let me go under your chin,
which is one of the most sensitive parts of a cat?
Would you let me just rub you under the chin like that?
In case you're here?
What, you're afraid of me?
Cause I'm such a bad guy?
Okay, okay.
Maybe I'll look too far.
I'm just a bad person.
I know, I know, it's okay, Kino.
You're probably right.
I'm just, I did something terrible.
What did I do?
Just explain.
what did i do this is what i do this is what it here here this is the hardest i ever touched my
cats that's as hard as it is as hard as i will be a little harder here here when i rub your neck
like that is that okay okay i'm sorry i went too far are you beautiful do you like piggy pillow
Rudy hi, Rudy
She even likes piggy pillow Rudy Rudy Rudy look piggy pillow look at piggy pillow
Did you care at piggy pillow sitting on you?
You can bother you at all I
Don't think he cares
He thinks piggy pillows cute too. That's your pit as my piggy pillow
I'm just a monster. I am a monster. He is regal
He does talk, he's a hi-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-
The piggy pillow is sitting right on top of you. Do you care?
They're beating that belly. They're beating that belly.
Oh, oh, no, no kiss. No kissing. Okay. Okay. Okay. I went too far. He doesn't know. No kissing the piggy pillow.
Sorry
Who's there that tricks tricks is back in the house
What where have you been? Where have you been?
Get over here. Get over your tricks. Come on. You're eating me out and tricks. Get over here
Come on over
What's wrong?
He's meowing inside.
Kino, don't say, what did I do to Danny Stranger?
What?
He came in meowing.
What did I do to Danny Stranger?
I gave Danny Stranger a smile.
Actually, he was more than a smile.
He like was really, really, I talked to him the next day.
He was like, thank you because
He's like, I had one of the best chats of my life.
I don't think he ever had that many people
in his chat in his life.
I really don't.
I looked over, he had 40 people.
Everyone left here and they went,
and he's cute, it's fine.
He was cute, right?
Everyone liked Danny, right?
That's like one of the best things about it is like,
He before he had to leave. I don't know if it was meant to be or whatever before he left
he had
Because he's been trying he said one of his videos had 1.2 million
Views on it, right? And so he had like 20,000 people like 20,000 subscribers and stuff from that
But he always had like two three at maybe I said three or four five six seven in the chat
But he had very few people in his shop, and I sent my chat over
He was having fun he had fun that's one of my things where I'm like
Maybe that was
Before he before he had to go he had fun. I mean he had like maybe that was one of his wishes of the earth
I don't know. I don't maybe I would
Danny was afraid
I can show you my last appearance. It was just like last week when I went on a show and I said I said Danny
I'm sorry because now because I was on your show
You got clipped because now they because now you're they say you're gay for pay, you know Danny said he said
So I don't care. Yeah, I don't care
They I know who I am. He's like, yeah, I sucked on a dildo for a couple hundred bucks for a woman
I don't think it was a woman Danny personally, but it's okay, you know, but yeah
He did that. I mean, someone paid him 200 bucks to suck on that deal, though he didn't get it.
Do I think he's gay for that? Well, maybe a little bit. I don't know. I'm just kidding.
I love you, Danny. Danny, he was sweet. I mean, he was like,
he was gonna let me buy his underwear and stuff like that, but it was too expensive.
Yeah, he sucked on Bilbo Baggins, you know the hobbit guy from the hobbit. He thinks this is the Bilbo Baggins
I want
Give him the best he was funny and awesome
He was and I I knew him I introduced him to Piranha. I met okay the first time I met Danny
I went to his chat and
I I was like you're really cute whatever he's like you're weird and then I use an emoji and he blocked me from the chat for using
emoji
He's like, he said I was trying to hit on the women in his chat because he only he had girlfriends and stuff
Right and then I introduced Piranha to him and Piranha said hey psyche's not a bad guy and then from then on
He was always cool. It's always cool
But you know, he said he said where's Piranha been I
Like I don't know Piranha told me that she would not talk to me until I got a job. So I blocked her
Because I was insulted because
Now you have to make a coffee. Yeah, I went to McDonald's, I had it on the drive-thru,
and so I went into the counter, and they're like, there's no coffee. I would spend like 20 minutes,
yeah. He was funny and awesome. He looked like Kid Rock. He was funny, awesome.
Rest in peace. Can you believe it? I can't believe you got shot in the chest. How bad would that be?
I have, um, I have two strikes, but they're too efficient. I mean, they're two strikes that can
be taken down. They're two strikes that can fight, but it's Betta and Alexandra. How worried should
Basically it's gone like
Unless one of them takes down the stripe
I'm saying goodbye because yeah, Bita and Alexander both struck me
Nobody really cares. I mean, it's like
Everyone cared about Sweet Pea, saying,
oh, oh, take down the, or like, you know,
write YouTube for Sweet Pea and stuff like that.
I mean, I even offered that.
And I did, I did, I talked to the YouTube about it
and stuff like that, and I felt bad.
I actually have a heart, I feel bad.
I mean, it's like, I don't think I was my fault, whatever.
You know what the difference is?
They don't feel bad.
They'll be as evil as they can be and they'll laugh. They'll be they'll be like, oh, thank God now. He won't talk about me
Right now and now he won't say or right. I don't know
Because I guess I guess me talking about
Here I am here I am and in the bottom of my heart, maybe I think
Maybe I think in the bottom of my heart. Maybe I think I might
survive
I've survived three times already
I'm not a quitter. I would like to have maybe like some people saying
What are you guys doing like
Great like what are you doing?
You guys you're like is it that time of the month not to be like that
Of course, they don't have a time of the month anymore. They're time of the month is all month now, right?
But um, I'm sorry. I don't know. I'm gonna be like, you know, I feel stup-
I shouldn't say that.
But I would love to have
like, like, you know, I would love to be like one
one percent of the love sweet pea gets
For just making fun of me and calling me a dirty fucking monster. I would like one percent of that as
love to me.
I won't leave. I won't leave until I have to but it's like
Right
What my tricks
Tricks tricks come here always looking at his lips tricks. Did you have a nice dinner?
You had a nice dinner huh tricks am I a monster tricks tricks my monster?
I'm a monster
What I'm a monster you're looking your lips look at him looking his lips you have a nice dinner. I know I know I had a big
A big platter of food. Oh, guess what else I got? I got other stuff for the cats. Hold on a second.
What else I got?
I got that.
Hello!
You've reached Psyche. You're on the air. Who is it?
Hello?
Who's calling me? Hello?
Can I help you? Hello?
Hello
Just playing my show they hung up
Look what I got has a big catnip on it on the side. Okay. Look sorry my nails are bad. Okay
You like this guys, huh?
That was the Algonquin vagina right there
Okay, that was bad. I don't know
That's cute, kitty. And look at this one.
Look at that one. How cute is that?
That's cute. I was like, oh, shit, that's so cute.
It looks like it's like a shirt my dad would wear kind of thing.
You want to get high on the catnip, guys?
Here, let's get high on catnip.
Let's see if we can get high on catnip.
Tricks, do you want to watch this?
Oh, shit. Tricks, Tricks, here.
Tricks
That was beaded with a voice box. Oh, you like this one tricks. Can I put can I pour this on you?
I mean they called oh you came over Lola here Lola
Here watch this
Catnap here here
My hand, here, Lola.
Here, go ahead, there you go.
Oh my God, look.
Yeah, 1076, goodbye 1076.
Are you like that, Lola?
Oh, look at there, she loves that.
That good?
That good, Lola?
Pumpkin, there's a pumpkin for you
Guess oh Lenore Lenore. Oh, we oh, they're calling back here
Hi, you're on the air
Hello
They're breed. I hear like a heavy breathing kind of thing. Hello, are you okay, sir?
Who is this? Who is it?
They hung up again. No, it's not new. These are my same tattoos here.
There's that one. I'm good with my tattoos. I think that was Mason.
And then, that one says Solve, and then I have my elbow, and that one says Lenore, but I have to get the L-A-N-O-R put in.
Okay, and I have one on my back.
I don't know. I don't know.
Bida, you're welcome to come over and hang out. I mean, come on. We're supposed to be cuddling in your bed, you know, a year ago.
Now, I'm a garbage in the earth, right?
Yeah, I do have Lilith on my back. I do know my back side. Oh my god
No, you're covered in that you're covered in the catnip
Hi, you're on the air
Hello
Hello, I can't hear you sir. Are you there? Hello? I
Hear like a heavy breathing
Are you wearing a are you wearing a screen mask? Hello
up again they keep hanging up oh and what are you you're covered in the catnip I see you covered in
catnip over there I know but they're they keep calling me though you're covered in catnip
It's rolling around in ecstasy.
I don't know.
I know it's an echo of my own stream, I heard myself talking and stuff, but...
They don't say hi, they keep calling me.
I thought it was like harassment at this point.
Oh, Rudy!
Do you want something to- look at Rudy coming over.
Wait, what's Lenore doing?
What's Lenore doing? Here.
You're stealing nor so hot. Lenore, don't fall off the couch! Don't fall off the couch!
Lenore!
My gosh, there she goes guys. Look at her
Lenora loves cat. Oh, look at her. Oh, there you come. Oh tricks game over. I mean, jeez
It's cute, huh
I'm a lucky guy.
Cause you're my, you're my, you're my, you know, you're mine.
You guys see last time I sent you photos of a meat
when the first night I got her.
I'll show you guys, you guys ever see these?
These are the cutest pictures.
There's my cat Oliver.
My cat Silly.
Hold on.
So here's my, here's me, my friend years ago, how much did an eighth, these were, those
were, they were, I got a good deal on those things.
Oh my God! Oh my God!
Lenore, you just knocked over the paper towels. Who's under there? You're under there watching?
Oh, it's just rolling around. We're just watching like an interest. Rudy, what's going on here?
It is. She is a woman. Yeah, there's my Russian friend.
This is when I lived in Glendale, another place. A little bit.
That was Alec. Alec was my...
cat but I'll show you um oh here she got me a pedicure one day a few are all
fucked up and she got me a pedicure that's that
I'll show you when I first got there this is Caleb oh look at these cats
Caleb was a cute cat
Caleb I think lives next door there. I think that's Lenore. Here's Lenore when she was a baby you can kind of see it a little bit
Because Russia loves cuddling with the kitty cats, so we're hanging out of this house
That was silly. Silly. Silly. Unfortunately the coyote got silly, but silly was a cutie. He would he would always lick the cats, too
Here's a little you like to lick the other cats. This is when I first got this when I first got a Lenore
You can see you can see she's like little eyes right there home. I'm sorry. You can't see that well, but yeah
There she is right there. See
Cute that's baby Lenore you ever saw baby Lenore
She's she's she's sitting up in my back way. She still does she still says my back
And there she is you can see a little face right there
You know little she was little she was I'm gonna cry
This is Oliver. Oliver was a big fat cat. Oliver was so cute too.
I had a little like a little bandana on him and stuff.
I don't know what happened to Oliver.
He was a big cat.
He was big and fat. He was such a big fat cat.
Hi, you're on the air.
Hello, hello
Hello
They're not saying anything hello
Are you there hello, it's just Texas
That was about
I think this was my cat Moira. Hold on. Look at this cat.
I think these cats are just in the neighborhood. Hold on one second. Hello?
Are you there? Hello?
Hello? Are you okay? Who is this? Is it Mason?
Mason, how are you? What are you calling?
Yeah, I'm okay, man.
What's going on? Why weren't you responding to me when I was talking to you before?
I was doing something at the same time. That's why I didn't respond. I was like watching you live in.
I was, you know, trying to call you at the same exact time.
I know. Well, how are you man? I miss you.
Yeah, I've been okay, man.
You're on the air. I don't know if you mind, but you're on the air so everyone can see. No one can see your number though, but yeah.
Yes, I got I still have your number from the time he gave it to me remember when I told you about the drum set being all destroyed and broken. Yeah, like this.
Well, yeah, I remember I gave my number to someone and then and then but you got it's okay I want you to have the number hey.
Do you want to say you actually gave it to me that day I actually was talking to you about like my drum set being like you know I don't have it anymore and stuff.
I want to do a team who drive. Oh my god. They cut the fire
Yeah, you're talking to my name any like last night or yesterday. Yeah, you saw Benny you say the interview with Benny
Yeah, so like when I was actually like, you know watching it like when I was like playing in my bed and stuff
Like on the TV. You were laying in your bed. What were you wearing?
Why are you calling on my phone and not on the show and I want to see your beautiful face
I just haven't been on because you know like uh mom's been different you know now like it's not the way it used to be
I mean, I know you're having a hard time too, but you know, I'm going through that as well
You are I'm sorry
You know yeah, you know be you know beta and uh beta struck my channel. Do you know that?
Yeah, I heard about that. Yeah, like last night
Alexander McQueen. Yeah. Yeah. He was, he was actually talking like to you, but you weren't there like after a long time, like you were gone. He was just still talking and stuff.
Well, are you like working on getting your drum set? Can I know like someone cut the cord?
I should be able to get it back, you know, built up like again, like if I can do it.
Do they have insurance for those?
my insurance like you can like say if you have a sometimes if you have like a car or like you know
a valuable item you get you pay like a little bit of insurance and then if anything ever happens to
it you get a new one for free but I mean I have a way I can uh there's an easy way I can get it done
like what happened to do that I think yeah well Alice McQueen says hi reality Nancy's here yeah the
Yeah
She's high
Yeah, do you want to come on the panel come on up how do you join the panel?
Yeah, I'd like you for you to I'm gonna put the link in the chat and you come on the panel in a minute, okay
Okay, I'm ready right now. Okay. Bye
I like it. I like a Mason's like, oh, you had some guy named Alex on the pan. Yeah, well, yeah,
Mason is our friend Alex. Like, you know, you know him very well. I mean, we love, we love Mason
and Alex. You're high. Oh, look at her. She's happy as can be.
Guys, I will I'm gonna pull I'm gonna post like I know you think oh, he's trying to make money off people and stuff like that
I really want to like like I only like share things if they're really cool
Like if they work for me, I would not share something just like I'll do such a thing. I actually use I have this bank
Okay, I had problems with banks for years
And so last night I looked at my bank statement and another cat's business
I look at my bank statement. I was I was overdrawn and stuff and I was like, oh shit. What's the rules for over over drafts?
Do you know I saw when I looked for the rules for the overdrafts? It said this is a non overdraft bank
You can spend up either like a hundred dollars to 250 depending on like how you get your money in the account
Over and they'll
Yeah, and they'll just cover with the next payment. It's like there's no overdrafts ever
So I'm gonna share I'm gonna share that bank on my community wall
That's pretty cool, huh?
The people over explain the lie. Well, it's like it's kind of yeah, it's a sperm bank. Oh, here's Mason
There's somebody on
Beat is and they everyone kept saying it looked like Tommy James and Mason together
I think his name was who's a guy for masks guys rocky something. He was rocky something
Did you say somebody looked like?
He was on beat his show last night his name is rocky something. What's that guy from the mask guys his name is Matt not Jim
Yeah, I'll find his name once again. His name was Rocky. He was in a movie with Cher.
His name was...
I heard about Cher. Yeah, I heard about Cher.
Rocky...
Um, Rocky Dennis. Have you heard of Rocky Dennis?
Uh, no.
Well, I don't think he looks like Mason. He does look like Tommy James though.
Guys, he looks exactly like Tommy James actually. I'll show you his picture.
Um, he doesn't look anything like Mason, but this is Rocky Dennis and he looks just like Tommy James
You guys want to see?
Think it's this one. It's like it's been a long time like right since I've been talking to you stuff again. I know. Do you miss me?
Yeah, that would be cool to come back, you know
See doesn't it look like Tommy James?
It was Tommy James. I never heard of such person. You never heard of such a person. Yeah. Well, he looks like this
We say like that. Yeah, there
We share. This is the real one. Kind of crazy looking at their home.
It's like, who is this person you're talking about? I've never heard of this.
Rocky Dennis. Well, have you heard it? There's a movie called mask. So look at this movie called mask has Sharon it
Let me look at it. You
Tell me what Jim Carrey carry one. It was a different one. His name is Rocky Dennis. Let me see it says here
It says Rocky Dennis was an American teenager who had cranio
CraneoDF B.C.L. Displaced CF an extremely rare psychotic brain disorder
or bone disorder. The condition results in neurological disorders during childhood,
and it says his life was the basis for the 1985 film mask.
And then it says, so Mass had his share played his mom.
It says, Peter Bogdanovich directed the 85 film,
Mass, I'm getting chills for some reason.
Rusty told Chicago reporter that his film was mostly accurate
with two major departures in reality.
The events occurred across 10 to 12 years,
not the one year depicted in the film.
And Dennis's older half brother Josh,
he was not in the film.
Okay, so I don't know, I don't really, I don't know.
It's like, yeah, it's kind of interesting.
He was in the movie.
That's his yearbook photo in 1977.
He looks like just like Tommy James though, guys, doesn't he?
What do you think?
Tommy James?
I think so.
Everyone okay?
I feel bad for him too.
I feel bad for him too, but you know what?
Like,
His mom loves him like that's a thing. He had a movie made about him and stuff, right? He had a disorder and stuff
Yes, I'm still here. Yeah. Yeah, I'm still here
Yeah, I'm about to open another beer up. I'm thinking of going maybe home. I need to check my message
What's up, Mason? Yeah, he was amazing. He was amazing. Did you think that other guy was good?
Did you think that other guy was good? Rocky Dennis or Tommy James?
I'll talk about the guy, Benny, that you were with, like, or talking yesterday, last night.
Benny was on the show last night. The police came when I was doing an interview with them last night.
Yeah, I'm Eric Stoltz. Yeah, I heard about that. I fell asleep. I
Fell asleep. I don't remember but I think no Benny left like he kind of like I don't know if I like scared him away or something
But I think he kind of got creeped out a little bit by the chat. I don't know. Hey, look at this guy
Isn't that cute?
Where'd you go, isn't that guy cute? Look at the little vampire guy
You can put oh here. Yes is back. You can put um catnip up his butt
You're back
Only person I was there was Alex like you know the same guy that you know talks to you
The guy Alex the Alex guy that was on there still he was so
Yeah, I love I love Alex. You know Alex is my friend
Yeah, he's your friend
But he's like you stayed on there when you were gone and then it was just him like, you know explaining stuff on there
You're explaining stuff. Yeah, there's a show. You remember Clarissa explains it all
There's like a show called Alex explains it all and he he actually gets in a block
That's where he's why that happened, yeah
Yeah, called Alex explains it all because he knows everything he does
Those it was something he had to get done like
Hey
She got him check out my text
Oh
You see the norm
Alex likes that. Do you see her? Do you see her to grab it? Look look watch watch this. You're talking about your cat?
Yeah, so of course. Yeah
Oh
So like you with your cat doing explain what something yeah, they're toy
It was funny
Unfortunately, you can't see the you can't see it anymore because um Alexander decided to strike the channel that I shared
I put the thumbnail as a picture of us at dinner
Um, I didn't think it was a, um, you know, like a, you know, it wasn't Monica Foster.
Right.
It wasn't like, you know, it wasn't her being rammed by five guys.
It is, you know, it's not still up because she, um, struck my channel for it.
So it was really.
But I guess you can get it on Rumble.
I think it will be on Rumble in a couple of days.
I went on Samanz and tried to talk to him.
They started talking about some other shit.
And then, oh, and then I came on to Samanz and I was beta.
And then she got a big introduction,
like all this cool stuff.
And it's like, whenever he plays my introduction,
it's like, oh, like a homeless person
and talks about biscuits and shit like that.
That's my, that's my,
That's my introduction but being a god is really cool. Like, you know, Korean cartoon shit. I get I always get like
Oh, here's here's psyche homeless
Bigging for a biscuit. That's what I get. So
So why do you want to go to jail like get last night? You're talking about you don't want to go to jail. I
Wanted to because I
That's the only probably the only place I'll be able to
Yeah
Free to go there. I don't think because you don't deserve that
I
You'll know but I'm a bad person Mason. Don't you think I'm a bad person like everyone else?
No, I don't think that I never said you were so why would you say that?
Well, everyone else thinks I'm bad like you know Alexander and Bita want to strike my channel like you know without
You know saying anything first. They just want to like you know take my channel down
Yeah
There's no reason for that so I don't think there is but but you have to talk to beta and
Alexander about that. Can you go to beat on Alexander's chat and talk to them for me? I
Don't really talk to them
But they would like to see you like beta talks about you and Alexander would like to meet you. I think
What do you think?
I've been over to like I talked to what she was on your channel before Alexander like I've been on here when she was on here
But that was about it like
Yeah, well, she's right now. She's right now. Hey. Hey, she says I'm a spiritual trafficker
Hey, well Kino casino. I don't know what it means. It's a little hockey puck Wi-Fi device that they use to perspire
Okay, how about that and I GG ER?
How about that? I don't know what it means though, right?
Yeah, I don't know what it means. That's what I'm saying.
I don't know what it means either, Mason. I'm the perfect guy for the biscuit though, right?
I'm the perfect guy. I'm the perfect guy.
It's a little funnier. They think I don't understand it's like a spying device.
Yeah, I know. Yeah, but yeah, I know what it is.
So, like, are you glad that I actually came back though to talk to you?
Of course! I love you!
I'm not in a gateway, but I thought we were cool. I thought we were friends. That's why you know
Okay, well it looks like tonight's not my night it was a very unlucky day for me there will be no
No, it's okay
I don't know what casino means.
Yeah, I don't know what Kino casino is.
I don't know what Kino, isn't Kino like a, yeah.
I don't know what it means.
But you know what I do know what it means?
Here, Mason, have you seen this clip?
I want to show you a clip on.
OK.
Do you like dolphins?
Yeah, I like dolphins.
Yeah, they're OK.
Do you like dolphins this much?
Hold on, I'll show you this little clip.
Here's my dolphin clip.
let's see. Watch this. Oh shit. That was an AI slot. Oh my god. Oh my god. I can't
show that. So like you didn't know what I was calling you. I was just calling you earlier
and you didn't know what the reason was. I didn't. Look, watch this. Watch this. Guys,
Here we go
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
What, did Jenner be, do you like that Mason?
Mason that yeah, yeah, that lady you see them saying hello. Yeah, I like it you like to do
You saw I'm saying hello to that lady
Yeah, so that yeah
That was a sweet clip
So I so you like that I came back though like to talk to you get her what what Mason are you balding your hairline?
Looks a little bit higher. What's wrong with your hair? Let's look at hi
There's nothing wrong with it
Nothing wrong with it. No animal abuse animal abuse that was animal abuse Kino
That dolphin abused that lady
Okay, how did the dog? How did the dog abuser side?
He helped her
No, that don't have the time of his life
The dolphin had the time of his life sort of that lady everyone's laughing if it was abuse
What would everyone be laughing unless they're really like sick people? No, I don't think people are sick like that
It was just funny the dolphin
Down to her attractive I
Was human abuse
It was
We're not both balding look guys. This is my hairline. So if you will say I'm balding look this balding
I've always had these like little horn. This is where my horns used to be
Hey ghost is fitting to crash out. Yeah
It's like how could I be balding though? I don't think that's happening. I
Don't think so either
Depends on hey birdie and joint don't even cry a homeward bound. Hey, go. Hey, it's almost a talk to you Mason. We have a guest home
Okay
Yes
Yeah, it is
Yeah
The fuck you only talk to Mason about what that Mason
Give me like literally
Yeah, I still hear you man
Yeah, I can hear you
Now I got I had to change my headphones to blue to my bed. How you doing, brother?
I'm good man
Yeah, I'm good
Yeah, I changed my headphones my bad. I had them plugged in by a bunch of Bluetooth
Wait, wait, go slow down
Are you still there yeah, so things are good. Oh, yeah with me. How about you?
Yeah, I haven't been here in a long time again like on the panel
It's gonna go if you hear if you hear movement, I'm gonna outside and smoke
I got you though. I haven't heard from you for a while now.
Not even the comments I have, but she didn't even give me a comment.
What's going on, dude?
What did you say? Sorry.
Are those dolphins that are happening?
You hear that yeah, but here's some dolphins like sounds
What are what are those dolphin sounds going on good
It's not me, it's probably not you.
It's probably Si.
Are you a fucking beer?
I was like
What's up?
How you doing, brother?
I was on the show earlier, brother.
what's up brother how you doing not very good that's what they said i was gonna call you but
i didn't want to be disrespectful because you're on a panel so you're fine
Yeah, how are you doing, man? I mean you're still alive. I got I got struck by beta and alexandra and they and they're they don't care
They're just like they just kind of laugh about it today. Did they how do you know that?
Did they say that they do it? No, I know I actually got the notification from YouTube
You've been stricken your channel struck because of a alexandra and beta and their full legal names are there too Monica Foster and
You're still alive though, right?
I am for now for now. Yeah
I mean something though it does mean something but you know
Just one little it's almost gone. It's almost gone ghost. I'm almost gone for a good your dreams are gonna come true
I'm almost gone guys. I don't know
Because beta and Alexander struck my channel
Yeah, but I was gonna make you like
Alex struck your channel I put a thumbnail of our dinner date when you know when we went to dinner together
I put that picture up with me and her in it and she struck it
How's that wrong though?
Yeah, I don't know
I probably have to do it. Probably shouldn't play that.
My mirror eyes they don't flinch in the storm They just watch the illusions form
I cut through the nerves which planes mid-flight Bleeding truth in the glare of the light
Now my legs are wide open alive Didn't care if I'd be willing to let it thrive
Watch me ascend while I'm shedding my skin Tangled in doubt but relive
SILENCE IN SHADOWS AND WISPER MY NAME
You lift me up
Just to test my flame
Watch me ascend on corn of pine
Fall in the park to rewind my mind
Silence in shadows breaking the crown
Lift me up I won't fall
Blessing the dark, praising the blue
The night is the canvas where visions move
My voice cracks thunder, my veins run blue
Hold me close, I'm becoming new
I come to the core, I switch into grace
I've built this world for my own mistakes
Now I'm full, no less no more
Didn't contain the feeling at all
Watch me as-
It is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it
Eyes closed, I fell through cosmic time
Now it's the magic you pose in mine
Circle divine, oh divine, you have a name
But I choose the line, oh I cut you free
It doesn't mean, right?
It's like, so can I talk to you then?
Tastes like sandalwood and heat
I follow the hush where the loader speaks
In the pause between my breath and my name
You arrive, soft thunder, blush, fire, flame
Eyes like vows I never said out loud
like mercy wrapped in something proud. I try to resist, but the cosmos leaves. Your beauty
is long, your silence means. And every year I would like armor turns to silk when you move through.
Lollipop
Tripura Sundari
Teach my hunger
Holy Geometry
Draw your shade, your crown, my skin
Let the world fall quiet
Let me in
Sugarcane, bowflower, aeroplans
You don't chase love
You invent it like this
Under your crown, blush, fire, I'm free
Lollipop
Enchant me endlessly
In every desire
The sweetest water the deepest fire
A palace hidden behind the heart
Nine gates opening one at a time
Your name is a key with a velvet bite a mantra that turns my dark to light and
When you speak, even shadows behave like wolves made gentle by your gaze
I don't want to rescue, I want your truth in my veins
I want the sweet discipline of your noose and your race
Lyle
flower-arrow bliss you don't chase love you invent it like this under your
crown blush fire I'm free, lolly time, chant me endlessly
in the city of the thousand-petaled hush where thought becomes nectar in time
becomes blush you sit at the center not distant not cold close enough to turn
Keep me in place not as a captive. No has chosen flame marked by blush fire that remembers my name
I've heard the saints whisper she's too bright to stare
But I like the danger and devotional
Let my ego dissolve like sugar and tea
I pray I'll be a slow surrender to she
If love is a spell, then cast it precise
Not to break me, beloved
To make me wise
For this undead crowd
What are you our home like what do you mean you want to go home my real home like not where is your real home in
heaven
You come on heaven. Yeah
Why would you want it? I mean you're not dead yet though. That's all we're going to death
I'm ready to go. I
Mean I feel that way too, but we can't be like that right?
It's like so what happened to the thing that is a buddy comes on here too. Sometimes he's not here today
I don't know where he is. I don't think he likes me anymore, but I am ready to go home and I
Know that I know they're the only reason I stay here
But yeah, they're like
It's like the only way you stay there because you're still like here like you're not dead
Not yet not yet, but that's what I'm saying
But thank you, but thank you guys nobody nobody like really wants to defend me about it
Nobody wants to like go to beat it and say anything no one wants to go to alexander and say anything
Yeah
I'm ready
The only thing I had for the only thing I had was the show and now that that's gone
I'm ready to go. Thanks guys. Have a good night